Seino!
Rattle channel go go go!
Ding-dong!
Please don't do that.
Today's project is "Don't be a moment!" Today's project is "Don for a moment!
Please ask them to stop.
I can't hear you.
It's not a project, but it's a project that I brought up,
Usually, it's the introductory don.
I don't know where it is, but it's not an intro.
The staff selected it.
The staff selects a part of a song and plays it for a moment, and we guess the part.
You said you didn't want to do it.
Are you sure?
We have a handler here, so if you make a mistake once, we'll call it a day.
Fair and square.
The other way around.
If you make a mistake and ring the wrong bell, you can't say that one word.
That's right. It's not a song.
Do you understand?
I am confident.
If it were our song, I think it would be totally fine.
Yes, it would.
It will work.
Yes, I'm sure. Let's go.
First question, let's start.
Two, one.
Okay.
Here, here, here, here.
Yes, yes, yes.
But it's the first time, so let's do it. It's the first time.
I can't say it like this. We'll be friends, right?
Sei-no. Which way?
Yes.
Okay, second question. Let's go.
Yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes.
What's wrong with me being popular?
Yeah!
What, what, what?
What is it?
No, I knew that.
But it wasn't just a moment.
What? What?
It was a little bit of a flush.
Isn't that what you're supposed to do?
I'm not at liberty to say.
Okay, Kirei, one point.
Okay, third question.
Third question.
What? What's this?
You should have just pushed it now.
I'm pretty sure it's not coming back.
Okay, let's try it.
Because I have to answer.
I'm glad you figured it out. That's great.
What is it?
Jagga-jagga-jungle.
I made a mistake.
What is it?
Can I ask you one more time?
There you are. That's Claire.
Claire, aren't you a genius?
Yes, I am.
Claire, you're a genius.
Eeeeeeeee...
But you never guess, do you?
No, but there's something...
Claire, earlier, when I was watching you guys...
I knew that if I didn't press the button before I knew what it was...
I knew I wouldn't make it in time.
So I pressed it right when it sounded.
But I didn't know... I didn't know.
But the sound was pretty deep.
It was just a very deep sound, like a gulp.
It's a camoneoca jungle.
I thought, "Well, maybe it's already dark in the jungle.
And I thought, "Wow, that's great.
Psychological warfare. Number one.
Claire, you're amazing!
I thought I was getting a hand job.
What a bummer.
Claire, one point for you.
I guess I'd better push anyway.
Question 4.
Ohhhhhh, don't you get it, boy?
Yeah.
I don't know what to do... push 3r... push faster...
and 6 are also bad.
and 6 are also bad... and I really don't have an answer.
2 is the fifth question...
I don't really know the answer...
Yes, yes...
Yes!
Rock steady.
I didn't get it.
I see what you mean.
What part?
Oh, wow.
That's great. That's great.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I think it's really great.
Huh?
Misaki, you're the only one with one point.
Not even close.
But, you know, I can hear you in the pylon.
Everyone knew by then.
Me?
Let's go on to the sixth question.
Yes, sir.
The ending.
All the way, all the way, all the way.
Why not?
It's right!
Yay!
I got lucky.
I see.
Kira, you're in the lead now.
It's a good seat... close.
Kira... one thing... if you think it's important...
Here's what I'll do.
You have good eyes.
Don't just do this.
Let's move.
Let's get out of here.
Excuse me.
And now the seventh question.
Oh, man, I'm losing.
You know what?
What? Wait a minute. I don't know.
You don't know, do you? That's it.
Go for it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You still have a right to an answer.
Okay.
Okay, in between.
Oh, my God.
Party time.
Well, then, make your move, make your move, make your move, make your move.
I can't answer that.
Yes!
Shangri-la.
Isn't that Hey Hey from Towa?
I didn't get this one either!
Clear is here.
Let's take a look.
It's Towa's voice, isn't it?
This is hard.
It's hard.
It's pretty hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'll be able to do it the next time, right?
I can do it. I can do it.
Start the 8th question.
Yes, I did.
It's me.
Uncool.
Damn!
I thought this was the rock stage.
No way!
Oh, I knew it.
The "ah-yu-LE-jiru".
It's like the first breath.
Oh, my God!
What?
I didn't get it.
Oh, no. Two more questions.
Question nine.
Here you go.
Bon appétit!
I'm sorry. I know what this is. I'm...
That was strong.
Swipe up.
It's music video.
Music video.
Oh, my God.
It's renewed.
We can't do it. We can't win.
Yes, you can.
Aja.
I'm doing IVHUNizi.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Meinung.
I know you're not here.
It feels so good to get it off my chest!
I'm talking about the last всего, but also the last tie...
I'm the world's only video player, right, Geico?
Shhhh...
Aaaaahhh!
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
No, that's a bit much, isn't it?
That was a bad one, haha.
Shoo-o-pah.
Aaaaahhh!
You just got me.
You're so loud.
Why are you so hard on yourself?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can I stop?
Shoooooooo!
That's great.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes! Yes!
Ooh.
I mean, um...
Yes. - Yes.
Um...
The backstabbing is perfect.
Hey, the media is perfect.
And the location is perfect.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Well, that means...
Yes, sir.
So that means
Yuzuha has 3 points
Claire has 4 points
Ms. Misaki
Mr. Killer
And Claire won!
Yay!
Well, this is...
It feels good to win, doesn't it?
It feels really good.
Because everyone got 3 points and only Claire got 4 points.
Aww...
No need to repeat
Aww.
What?
BTW.
What, what, what, what?
I'm just happy for you.
Congratulations!
It was an opportunity that Yuzu brought up to me.
It's really frustrating to lose after you brought it up.
I'd like to do it again.
Let's take revenge.
Let's do it again.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel, click the "Good" button, and leave a comment.
See you soon!
This time I'm wearing a costume by D-Holic!